It's been a while.
久しぶりです
I didn't know I was in a car.
車に乗っていることを知らなかったから
I hadn't ridden it before.
前に乗っていませんでした
A car lot or something.
車場とか
I'm a little surprised that I don't have an image of a car.
車のイメージがなくて、ちょっとびっくりしています
Why are you driving today?
今日はなんで車なの?
You see, there is actually one more person who is having trouble.
あのね、実はもう一人摩擦います
Another person?
もう一人?
girl?
女の子?
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
What's the matter?
何の事?
What do you mean?
何の事ですか?
There's a young girl.
若い女の子がいるのよ
It's my job though.
自分のお仕事なんだけど
That child is so pure and cute.
その子ね、超ピュアで可愛いのよ
You mean a high school girl, right?
女子高生ってことでしょ?
You mean my student?
教え子ってこと?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I don't think I've ever talked to her since she's a high school girl.
女子高生ってことで喋ったことないかも
Ah, that's good.
あ、いいじゃん
On the contrary.
逆にね
It might be a social study.
社会勉強になるかもしれない
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Even though it's a model-like model.
モデル並みのモデルだけども
Model pheromones?
モデルのフェロモン?
I would like you to tell me that,
そういうのを教えてあげてほしいんだけど、
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
There's a part of me that likes to make clean things dirty.
ちょっとね、きれいなものは汚したいみたいなとこもある
After all, that's what we were talking about when we were over there.
だって向こうにいる頃にそういう話してたじゃん
I agree.
そうだね
Don't think so and say anything nice.
そう思って、いいなんも言わないで
I've already set it up.
すでにもうセッティングしちゃったんだよね
Do you know that that child is me?
その子は私ということを知ってる?
I did say that there was someone who introduced me.
一応紹介した人がいるとは言った
I don't think there are any details.
詳しいことはないみたいな
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっとドキドキする
I'm looking forward to it though.
楽しみなんだけど
I'm thinking about going somewhere with the three of us.
3人でどっか行こうかなみたいなことを思ってるんだけど、
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じ
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみです
I'm kind of nervous.
なんか緊張しちゃう
I'm actually there already.
もう 実はそこにいる
Eh, are you there?
え、いるの?
You had better go quickly.
早く行ってあげたほうがいい
I can wait.
私 は待てればいい
Don't get excited.
ドキドキしないで
cold.
寒い
Sorry.
ごめんね
Did you wait?
待った?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
It's raining.
雨が
The teacher came by car.
先生車で来たんだよね
Yay!
やったー
Going out again.
またお出かけ
Someone came before me, so please introduce me.
前に来た人がいるから紹介してね
fun.
楽しみ
get nervous.
緊張する
Shy person.
人見知りやし
Shyness.
人見知り
Only the beginning.
最初だけ
Because it's a good voice.
いい声だからね
It's the atmosphere.
雰 囲気よ
It's cold.
寒いです
It was small.
ちっちゃったよ
It was raining all at once.
一気に雨でそっちゃったから
What do you think?
どうですか?
Ah, it's happening right now.
あ、コロコロ今だ
this.
これ
a,
あ、
there was.
いた
cold.
寒 い
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You have an older sister, right?
お姉さんいるでしょ?
in front.
前に
Sister.
お 姉さん
It's a uniform!
制服じゃん!
Let me ride in the back.
後ろに乗ってあげな
Ride in the back.
後ろに乗る
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
There was a mountain.
山があった
Mom has an outbreak.
お母さん発生だ
Please be careful.
気をつけてね
sorry.
ごめんなさい
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Okay.
よ いしょ
Close it.
閉めてよ
yes.
はい
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
get nervous.
緊張する
I can't see it.
見られない
Take a look.
ちょっと見てみて
It's super cute.
超かわいいの
He's a beautiful driver.
綺麗な運転手さんです
Isn't it so cute?
め っちゃかわいくない?
cute.
かわいい
Yes, it's cute.
そう、かわいいの
Congratulations.
めでたい
scared.
怖い
get nervous.
緊張する
I thought that I would include the two Shinboku,
2人のしんぼくを含めてもらうと思って、
I like strawberry picking because of the timing.
時期的にもちょっとあれだから、 いちご狩りとか好きしい
Isn't it?
じゃない?
everyone.
み んな
not at all.
全然
It might be my first time in a while.
私久々かも
first time.
初めて
first time?
初めて?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's my first time.
初めてだって
first time.
初めて
Long time no see.
久々
I don't dislike it.
嫌じゃないよね
i wanna go.
行きたい
I was thinking of going strawberry picking.
いちご狩りに行こうかなと思って
I like strawberries.
いちご好き
I love strawberries.
いちご大好き
I want you to eat something that looks good on strawberries.
いちご似合うもの食べてほしい
Looks good on me.
似合いそう
I want to go.
行きたいです
Please start strawberry picking.
いちご狩りに始発してください
Yay!
やったー
It's cold.
寒いね
You can see it.
見えちゃうね
Add some hair.
ちょっと髪の毛入れて
amazing.
すごい
Because it's warm inside.
中温かいから
cold.
寒い
Bare legs?
生足?
Bare legs.
生足
It's cold, isn't it?
寒いよね
This is terrible.
やばいよ
hair.
髪の毛
Go ahead.
先に行って
Close it.
閉めて
I was surprised.
びっくりした
Can I go wherever I like?
好きなところに行っていい?
cute.
かわいい
There are lots of strawberries.
いちごがいっぱいいる
Fold it like this.
こうやって折るように
It's difficult to cover.
かぱて難しい
Blood came out.
血が出ちゃった
Oh no.
やば
I have to lick it.
舐めないと
That's a lie.
嘘です
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
I got it.
取 れた
delicious.
おいしい
how was it?
どうだった?
I got it.
取れました
delicious.
おいしい
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
cute.
かわいい
delicious.
おいしい
It's delicious.
おいしいね
this?
これ?
I got it.
取れた
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
cute.
かわいい
It's delicious.
おいしいよ
It's me, right?
ど にぼくでしょ
This one is cool.
こっちやがりこい
It's true.
ほんとだ
Very different.
めっちゃ違う
It's really big.
めっちゃでかいのあるし
Let's eat.
食べよう
delicious.
おいしい
sweet.
甘い
delicious.
おい しい
Did you eat all this?
これ全部食べてた?
I'll do everything for you.
全部セーハンしてくるわ
It's really big.
めっちゃ大きいですね
Please go ahead.
どうぞどうぞ
Are you drinking a lot here?
ここいっぱい飲んでる?
Yeah, a lot.
うん、 いっぱい
Take a bite.
一口食べて
Super sweet.
超甘い
hot.
熱い
How many did you eat?
何個食べた?
full.
いっぱい
sweet.
甘い
It seems like I can't take this home with me,
これ持って帰れないみたいだから、
already.
もう
I can't go home.
帰れない
After taking it in your mouth once.
一回いっぱい口の中に含んでから
Like a squirrel.
リスみたいに
delicious.
おいしい
Isn't it nice around here?
ここら辺とかいいんじゃない?
This is really big.
これめっちゃかいです
Don't eat it?
食べな?
Aren't you going to eat it?
食べないの?
Can I eat it?
食べていいですか?
This is all a lie.
これきめごまかいよ
Kime sesamekai?
き めごまかい?
What is Kimegomakai?
き めごまかいって何ですか?
Look, look.
見て見て
It's a joke.
きめごまかい
Binding.
縛りかい
real?
ほんと?
Adults definitely don't do that.
絶対なんか、やらねえ大人は
Not at all.
全然違う
Is it delicious?
おいしいですか?
After all, it's delicious all over the world.
世界中おいしいやっぱり
The one I ate myself.
自分から食べたやつ
Benny Hoppe?
ベニーホッペ?
Let's eat.
食べよう
I can't stop, Ichigo.
止まんないよね、いちごとか
I can't stop.
止まんない
A girl's dream.
女子の夢
Can you eat this?
これが食べれるの?
lie.
嘘
That's a lie, absolutely.
嘘だ、絶対
Can I ask you not to deceive me like that?
そうやって騙さないでもらっていいんですか?
This is nice and smooth.
これスムーイっていいじゃん
Even a sip.
一口さえ
It's bright red.
真っ赤だ
It's going to be crazy again.
またトッキリするじゃん
Are you saying something?
何 か言ってる?
I haven't said anything.
何も言ってない
Did you hear something?
何か聞こえたかな?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I'm also embarrassed by what happened to me.
された私も恥ずかしい
I'll give you something in return.
お返しをいたしますね
I wonder what episode this is.
これ何の回なんだろう一体
cute.
かわいい
delicious.
おいしい
cute.
かわいい
It might be a little stiff.
ちょっと硬いかも
Did you say something?
何か言った?
It might be a little stiff.
ちょっと硬いかも
No.
ダメだ
Because I don't want you to get hurt.
怪我しちゃいけないから
It may still be a little stiff.
ちょっとだけまだ硬いかもしれない
Why?
なんでだろう?
It's not sexy.
色気がないな
You ate smoothie.
スムーイ食べたね
I ate a lot.
結構食べた
Why don't you eat the one that's full?
いっぱい入ってるの食べない?
It's already stored away.
もう収納された
I ate a lot.
いっぱい食べた
I'm full.
お腹いっぱいです
It was a bit cold.
ちょっと寒かったね
It was cold.
寒かった
It's warm inside.
中は温かくて
I don't even eat hot food.
温かいものでも食べない
It's cold, isn't it?
寒いよね
It's a little too cold.
ちょっと寒すぎる
Is there anything around here?
ここ ら辺何かある?
I feel like I'm close to outrate.
アウトレート近くなった気がする
Are you going shopping?
買い物行く?
I want to go.
行きたいです
How about a price for your sister?
お姉さんにお値段したら?
Are you going to buy it?
買っちゃうの?
Please buy nothing.
何も買ってください
I'll buy anything.
何も買っちゃうよ
Let's go then.
じゃあ行こう
I did it.
やった
It was my first time here.
初めて来た
Outrate.
アウトレート
I guess I haven't been there much.
あんまり行ったことないかもね
Ah, Chinese kitchen.
あ、 チャ イニーズキッチン
It's Chinese.
中華だ
It's chicken.
チキンだ
This container is cute.
可愛いね、この入れ物が
chicken?
チ キン?
chicken.
チキン
Is it Western food?
洋食かな?
Something like omelet rice.
オムライスとか
With Swaina.
スワイナと
Let's go anywhere.
どこでも行こう
I'll eat anything.
なんでも食べます
anything?
なんでも?
Then please eat this.
じゃあこれを食べてください
Why do you do it like that?
なんでそういう風にしめるんですか?
Please stop.
や めてください
looks delicious.
美味 しそう
Is it pretty good?
結構いいの?
Let's do it here.
ここにしましょう
Looks delicious and very pink.
美味しそう、めっちゃピンク
It's a hotpot.
鍋ですもんね
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
Looks hot.
熱そう
It's awkward because I'm used to seeing it.
見慣れてるの気まずい
What should I do about this?
これどうしたらいいの?
I don't know.
知 らないもんね
It's tough.
ガツイって
looks delicious.
美味しそう
It's warm.
温かいです
hard?
辛い?
It's not spicy at all.
全然辛くない
It says it's a little spicy.
ちょっと辛いって書いてある
this?
これ?
Tofu?
豆腐?
potato?
ポテト?
What is it?
何だろう?
What is that?
何なのそれは?
Is it tofu?
豆腐かな?
Looks like tofu.
豆腐っぽい
It's tofu.
豆腐です
Sesame tofu.
ゴマ豆腐
Can I look back on this?
これ振り返していいんですか?
豪華
Excuse me, go first.
すみません、お先に
I'll go out of my way to show it to you from the beginning.
最初からわざわざ見せちゃう
Around that at first.
最初そのあたり
Yeah.
うん
After all, the beauty of Hitsumabushi is that it tastes twice as good, right?
やっぱ二度美味しいのがひつまぶしの良さでしょ?
After all, don't keep it warm, you'll just eat it as is.
結局いつも温かいしないでよ、そのまま食ってるんだよ
I've never enjoyed something delicious again.
二度美味しいを楽しんでないんだ
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
delicious.
美味しい
looks delicious.
美味しそう
Looks really happy.
すごい幸せそう
delicious.
美味しい
I ate all of this.
これ全部食べちゃった
I'm hungry.
お腹が
My stomach hurts.
お腹がやばいね
It's the last bite.
ラ スト一口だよ
It was delicious.
美味しかった
Are you hungry?
お腹された?
Yeah, happy.
うん、幸せ
I'm also hungry.
私もお腹やばい
Thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでした
It's story time.
話見タイムだね
From here, from here.
こっから、こっからが
This is what I'm good at.
こっからが得意ね
It's story time.
話見タイムだよ
My heart is pounding.
ドキドキする
amazing.
すごい
It feels like doing something bad.
悪いことするって感じ
Isn't she so wet?
ビッチョビチョなんじゃないの?
Coming soon.
もうすぐに
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいですね
I'm so excited.
ドキドキしちゃうね
That kind of youth.
そういう青春時代とか
There it was, there it was.
あった、あった
Now is the time of youth.
今、まさに青春時代
I can go home now.
帰れる、今
That's what it is.
そういうこと
A page from my youth.
青春の1ページにね
Isn't it?
ないそうじゃない?
Your heart is pounding, right?
ドキドキするでしょ
I'm excited too.
こっちもドキドキしてる
Are you watching over me?
見守ってますか?
That's awkward.
気まずいね
Will you watch over me?
見守るの?
How would you confess?
どんなふうに告白するんだろうとか
It starts with a confession.
告白から入るんだ
I'll try my best.
頑張ってみる
It's so messed up.
すごいめちゃぶり
Isn't that a huge mess?
すごいめちゃぶりじゃない?
Is there something you want to do?
何かしたいことあるの?
something.
何 か
There are many things I want to do.
したいことはいっぱいある
Cute, because she said it was cute.
かわいい、かわいいって言ってたから
Cute, I want to be cute.
かわいい、かわいいしたい
Cute, cute.
かわいい、かわいい
Toddle.
よちよちして
Are you toddling?
よちよちしてるんですか?
I want to toddle.
よちよちしたい
Let's do it together.
一緒にしよう
together?
一緒に?
Is it different?
違うの?
together?
一 緒 に?
cute.
かわいい
Hair is smooth.
髪の毛サラサラ
cute.
か わいい
Smooth.
す べすべ
cute.
かわいい
No, I want to take it home.
だめだ、持って帰りたい
yes?
そう?
What if you come here?
こっち来たら?
yes.
はい
terrible.
やばい
What should I do?
どうしよう
Is the photo taken from behind?
後ろから撮られてるの?
It's twilight, isn't it?
黄昏れてるよね
It's not time to be twilight, but not yet.
黄昏れてる時間じゃないけど、まだ
It's called the twilight back.
黄昏れてる背中っていうことで
I thought I was wearing a uniform too.
私も制服着てるって思って
terrible.
やばい
Yamanaka.
山中
Uniforms are erotic.
制服がエロいもん
I'm the man.
私が男役なんだ
yes?
そう?
I'm really excited.
めっちゃドキドキする
difficult.
難しい
I don't like it, it's a bit too much.
嫌だ、ちょっとめっちゃ
What are you doing?
何してる?
Over here.
こっちで
why?
なんで?
reference?
参考?
Okay.
いいよ
It's like the two of them are sophisticated.
精緻みたいな感じだからね、二人は
Now, Yuri's precision.
今ね、ゆりの精緻ね
That's right.
そうだよね
Isn't he a great actor?
すごい男役じゃない?
I.
私
What should I do?
どうしたらいい?
Is it okay to play the role of the older sister?
お姉さん役でいい?
That's it.
って
It's not a role, she's an older sister.
役じゃないし、お姉さんだし
That's right.
そうだよね
What do you want to do?
どんなことしたいの?
I wonder what it is.
なんだろうな
If it's possible...
せっかくだったら...
What is it?
なんだろう?
Please stop.
やめてください
Something naughty that you've never experienced before?
ちょっと 経験したことないようなエッチなこと?
I would like you to tell me.
教えてほしいなと思います
Oh no, it's cute.
やばい、かわいい
Aggressive brisket.
積極的ブリスキー
It's getting a little hot.
ちょっと熱くなってきた
Is it okay to just wear a jacket?
上着だけでもいいかな?
You don't have a jacket.
上着ないじゃん
By jacket, I mean.
上着、ということは私は
So one piece at a time.
じゃあ1個ずつ
Is that me?
それ、私、あれ?
I'm faster.
私の方が早く
I see.
そ っか
That's no good.
だめだよね
Just without a jacket, for a moment.
上着なくだけだよ、ちょっと
My heart is pounding.
ドキドキする
A shirt is nice.
シャツっていいな
Cunning.
ずるい
I'm already touching it.
もう触ってる
I'm already there.
私早くももう
When?
いつの間に?
They say it's a baseball area.
野球圏だって言うから
Even though I'm not playing rock, paper, scissors in the baseball area.
野球圏じゃんけんしてないのに
But I thought that if I took out one piece, I would also take out one piece.
でも1枚抜いたら、私も1枚抜いていくスタイルかなと思って
I want to try to get it now.
今、取ろうとしたいね
I'm not trying to take it.
取ろうとしてない
Your sister's smoothness.
お姉さんのすべすべ
I also want to touch your back.
それは私も背中をおさわりしたい
I feel like I want to touch you.
おさわりしていきたい気持ちがあるよね
This is the shirt my mom used to wash for me.
お母さんが洗ってくれてるシャツだよ
That's even erotic.
それすらエロいよ
But isn't it a waste to take off uniforms?
でも制服ってさ、脱がせるのもったいなくない?
Hey, it's a waste.
ねえ、もったいない
It's a fatherly way of thinking.
親父的思考だ
What should I do?
どうしよう
Where should we attack?
どこから攻めていこう
Isn't it here?
ここじゃない?
As expected.
やっぱ
I guess so.
やっぱそうだよね
I thought so too.
私もそう思ったの
If you ride here.
乗ったらここ
We are now allowed to do as we please.
もう私たちが好きなようにさせてもらってる
You want to see it, right?
見たいでしょ
You'd like to see it.
見たいだろうね
Scary, for two people.
怖い、2人に
I'm scared.
怖がってる
cute.
かわいい
It has a ribbon.
リボンついてるよ
cute.
かわいい
It feels good already though.
もう気持ちいいんだけど
It's naughty.
エッチだわ
Is the doctor play about to begin?
お医者さんプレイが始まっちゃうの?
It will begin.
始 まります
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Yurai-chan.
ゆらいちゃん
white!
白!
We have to record it together.
2人で記録しないと
Hey me.
ちょっと私
Are you going to take it off?
脱いちゃうの?
hot.
熱い
Look at this lady's underwear.
見て、このお姉さんの下着
It's naughty.
エッチだ
Look behind you, behind you.
後ろ見て、後ろ
Look at that butt.
見て、お尻が
My butt.
お尻が
I was a little poor and could only buy something made of thin fabric.
少し貧乏で生地が薄いのしか買えなかったんだ
That's right.
そうなの
I don't even have to paste it.
貼ることもない
terrible.
やばい
Will you fix it right away?
すぐ直しちゃう?
I don't like it.
嫌だな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
cute.
かわいい
It's super beautiful.
超きれいだね
terrible.
やばい
It's super beautiful.
超きれいだよ
Right?
でしょ?
terrible.
やばい
Super beautiful.
超きれい
I'll hold it down.
押さえちゃう
I'll bend it.
曲げちゃう
scared.
怖い
It's super beautiful.
超きれいだな
What's going on behind this?
これ後ろどうなってるの?
behind?
後ろ?
Back, normal.
後ろ、普通で
Is it normal?
普通なの?
cute.
かわいい
It's a race.
レースじゃん
Wait a minute, your butt is already showing.
ちょっと待って、もうお尻が透けている
Your butt is transparent.
お尻が透けているじゃん
Look.
ほら
Super beautiful.
超きれい
Very smooth.
めっちゃスベスベ
That's how you do that before me.
そうやって私より先にそういうことをするのね
It's not pretty.
きれいじゃない
It's dangerous though.
やばいんだけど
Would you like a skirt?
ちょっとスカートはよろしいですか?
I'm proactive.
僕は積極的
Walk on your feet.
足で歩いて
terrible.
やばい
Shirt, tie.
ワイシャツ、ネクタイ
That's amazing.
すごいですね
I'm nervous.
緊張してる
Red face.
顔赤い
My face is turning red.
顔が赤くなってる
cute.
かわいい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Your body is really hot.
めっちゃ体熱いね
No, it gets really hot.
いや、めっちゃ熱くなっちゃう
I touched it.
触 っちゃった
Well then, let me leave you alone for a moment.
じゃあちょっと私も抜かせちゃおう
Leave it out.
抜かして
Let it be as it is done to you.
されるがままだ
I had a great experience right now.
すごい経験をしてました、今
But me too, JK.
でも私もだって、JKは
It's my first time being a JK.
JKは初めてだからな
It's wet, isn't it?
濡 れてるよね
It's wet.
濡れてるよ
Are you wet already?
もう濡れてるの?
cute.
かわいい
It's wet.
濡れてる
It's early.
早いね
It's pure.
ピュアだね
Excuse me for a moment.
ちょっと失礼します
Oh no, it's beautiful.
やだ、きれい
cute.
かわいい
Your bra is cute too.
ブラもかわいいね
It's super beautiful.
超きれいだよ
terrible.
やばい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Poor.
貧相な
I still have the body of a child.
まだまだ子供の体が
why?
なんで?
It's beautiful, very beautiful.
きれいよ、超きれい
I can see Iriyan.
入林見えてる
Because I can't see it.
見えてないから
Don't get nervous either.
私も緊張するな
Touch it, it's wet here.
触ってみて、ここ濡れてるよ
real?
ほ んと?
It's wet.
濡れてるよ
It's true.
ほんとだ
You did a terrible job.
やばいやったかいもん
When did you feel it?
いつ感じちゃったの?
No, it's already time for a lady like this to start taking off her clothes.
いや、もうこんなお姉さんが脱ぎ始めたらもうね
Is that so?
そうなの?
I could see it.
私見えた
I saw it too.
私も見た
I'll give you half of this.
こっち半分あげる
Understood.
わかった
Oh no, it's embarrassing.
やだ、恥ずかしい
It's super beautiful though.
超きれいなんだけど
It's cute, isn't it?
かわいいよね
cute.
かわいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I'm doing it.
エーしてる
cute.
かわいい
terrible.
やばい
That's erotic.
それはエロいよ
It's visually stunning.
視覚的に素晴らしいね
This is erotic.
これはエロいわ
Shall I help you?
ヘルプラしちゃおうか
Do it with me too.
私も一緒にして
Come here.
こっちして
Over here.
こっちね
hot.
熱い
So cute.
すごいかわいい
Sorry, my hands are a little cold.
ごめん、ちょっと手冷たいよね
Wow, looks like we're doing something wrong.
すごい私たち悪いことしてるみたい
Am I doing something wrong?
悪いことしてる?
I'm doing something bad.
悪いことしてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Seriously?
まじ?
Yeah.
うん
I was a bit embarrassed so I went in.
なんかこっち恥ずかしくて入っちゃった
cute.
かわいい
It's very beautiful, but completely white.
すごい綺麗なんだけど真っ白で
Sister,
お姉さん、
I lent you that too.
そ っちも貸したよ
I lent you that.
そっち貸したね
Oh, I was lent it to you.
あ、私貸されたのね
I should also commemorate that.
それを私も記念すべき
I also want to share this memorable piece.
記念すべき一枚私も流したい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Yay.
やー
Aww, that's cute.
やー、かわいい
I saw it.
見 ちゃった
見ちゃった
I saw it too.
私も見ちゃった
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
Want to check it out?
確認してみる?
Can I check?
確認していいですか?
Is it okay if I check it?
確認させていただいてよろしいですか?
There's a new one coming.
新作入りますね
This is so embarrassing.
これめっちゃ恥ずかしいわ
What should I do?
どうしよう
Super beautiful.
超綺麗
Isn't it super beautiful?
超綺麗じゃない?
Everything is beautiful.
なんも綺麗
beautiful.
綺麗
I touched it, I touched it.
触っちゃった触っちゃった
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗
cute.
かわいい
Do you want to taste it?
味見する?
Is it okay?
いいの?
a bit.
少し
Looks happy.
嬉しそう
May I excuse you?
失礼していいかしら?
Did you see if I was wet earlier?
さっき濡れてるか見たら?
Shall we take a look then?
じゃあ見ようか
nostalgic.
懐かしい
Oh, it's wet.
あ、濡れてる
I'm pulling the strings.
糸引いてるよ
cute.
かわいい
It's naughty.
えっちなんだね
I'm taking pictures.
撮ってるちゃんと
Something to keep in mind.
念すべき
cute.
かわいい
delicious.
おいしい
lick
舐
Did you get married?
め られちゃった?
I got licked.
舐められちゃった
I licked it.
舐 め ちゃった
Lick it.
舐めて
Lick it?
舐めて?
How do you lick it?
どうやって舐めるの?
delicious.
おいしい
cheese.
チーズ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Do I have to drink it?
飲みつけないと?
Super beautiful.
超キレイ
Why not try a little chew?
ちょっとチューとかしてみたら?
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
vice versa.
逆に
good?
いい?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Shall we do it with three people?
3人でしちゃう?
Chew with 3 people?
3人でチュー?
new?
新しい?
That's new, isn't it?
新しいね、それは
Please go first.
先にどうぞ
Because it's a big deal.
せっかくだから
thank you.
ありがとう
But you give it to me, at first.
でも私にくれるのね、最初は
I'll be waiting.
待ってます
Well, I guess I'll go first.
じゃあ私から行く感じね
Wait there.
待ってて、そこで
I'll be waiting.
待ってます
Are you embarrassed?
照れる?
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい
Is the steep one good?
ティープなやつはいいの?
Wait, then there.
待ってて、じゃあそこで
I'll go pick you up.
私が迎えに行く
It's new.
新しいね
Hehehe.
うふふ
How can I influence that?
そ こ私どうやって左右するのかな?
fun.
楽しい
This lady is a little bit like this, check it out.
このお姉さんはちょっとね、こうしたかをチェックしてみて
This way.
こっち
I'm fine.
私はいいよ
It's no good, give me a prick like this.
ダメだよ、こんなチクリ出して
I haven't put it out.
私は出してない
I'm just excavating it.
発掘してるだけじゃん
I haven't put it out yet, chikubi.
出してないもん、チクビ
Adult chikubi.
大人のチクビ
No, no, no chikubi.
違う違う、チクビは出してない
Do you mean to take turns?
交代するってこと?
That's right.
そうだよ
I feel more embarrassed when I get it.
される方が照れる
Look.
ほら
What is hora?
ほらってなんですか?
ほらって何?
Sister, look at this.
お姉さん、これほら
If you don't take a picture of your sister, this is it.
お姉さん撮らないとこれ
Then please take a picture.
じゃあ撮ってください
Where is it?
どこにあるの?
Is this it?
これか
this?
これ?
perhaps.
多分
I was able to take a picture.
撮れた
Sister.
お姉さん
Big sister.
お姉さんさ
It came out.
出てきたよ
出 てきた
Wait a minute, that's really embarrassing.
ちょっと待って、本当に恥ずかしいじゃん
I understand how you feel.
気持ちがわかった
sorry.
ごめんなさい
What should I do?
どう し ようかな
I'm really embarrassed.
ちょっと本当に恥ずかしい
It's really embarrassing.
本当に恥ずかしい
What is dangerous?
危ないって何?
My hands are in danger.
手が危ない
why
なんで
that?
それ?
That's right, Racha.
そ っちなめた、ラチャ
Participate.
参加して
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
It's embarrassing, really.
恥ずかしい、本当に
Looks like a cat.
お猫みたい
Wait a little longer.
もうちょっと待って
What do you mean?
どういうことですか?
Look, your sister's pussy.
見て、お姉さんのマンコム
No, no, no.
違う違う違う
It's beautiful, so beautiful.
綺麗だよ、すごい綺麗
Amazing, amazing.
すっごい、すっごい
You're doing great, sis.
すぶすぶだよね、お姉さん
Thank you, Usemu-san.
ありがとう、うせむさんの
Sister, you need to do what you just did.
お姉さんさっきやったことやらないとね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Shall I tell you?
教えてあげようか
I see, it's an insurance class.
なるほど、保険の授業
This is called Clintoris.
これがクリントリスと言います
Where is it?
どこですか?
where?
どこ?
This, this, this.
これ、これ、これ
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
amazing.
すごい
Your sister is also wet.
お姉さんも濡れてる
beautiful.
綺麗
I got wet in the chair.
お椅子の中濡れちゃった
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
here?
ここ?
terrible.
やばい
Shall we bring out Yopoo?
ヨープー出してみる?
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
Wait a minute, that's so embarrassing.
ちょっと待って、めちゃくちゃ恥ずかしい
What should I do?
どうしよう
terrible.
やばい
I'm taking pictures.
撮ってますよ
I did it.
やった
や った
A little embarrassed
ちょっと恥ずか
Yes.
しい わ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
No, it's erotic.
いや、エロいよね
It's definitely erotic.
確実にエロいよね
Induced shape.
誘導される形
You're being guided.
誘導されてるんだね
I want to see that.
そういうの見たい
I see.
なるほど
Oh, I'm preparing.
あれ、準備してる
It's a bit of a pain.
ちょっとお気持ちしごい
amazing.
すごい
It's standing really well.
すごい立ってる
It's true.
本当や
fun?
楽しい?
Look at me.
見てて
fun?
楽しい?
Jackin'.
ジャッキンして
Jackin, pop!
ジャッキン、ポン!
I entered.
入った
How do I use this?
これどうやって使うの?
Something bad happened.
やばいのがわたっちゃった
Have you ever used this?
これ使ったことある?
It's the edge of Ru.
るのエッジだね
Please excuse me for a moment.
ちょっと失礼しますね
Seishi used it, right?
せいしが使ったんだよね
Ah, that's why I'm preparing it.
あ、だからさ、仕込んでるじゃん、
already.
もう
before me.
私の前に
feet.
足
How do I change this?
これさ、どうやって変えるの?
That won't change any further.
それが、それ以上変わんない
It can't change any more.
これ以上変わんない
That's Max.
それがマックス
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It feels good.
気持ちいいって
terrible.
やばい
Ah, I can't stop.
あ、なんか止まんない
Can I participate?
参加してもいい?
Because I can't help it.
しょうがないから
already?
もう?
Because I can't help it.
しょうがないから
How
仕方
do not have.
ない
In the middle?
真 ん中に?
Yeah.
うん
Like a harem?
ハーレムのように?
Facing this way.
こっち向きで
There was a harem facing me.
こっち向きにハーレムだった
Ah, good.
あ、いい
This is the best.
これ最高
Everyone shoo.
みんなでシュー
Do we all like choux?
みんなでシュー好きなの?
Whoosh.
シュー
cute.
かわいい
Are you excited?
ドキドキする?
This way.
こっち
I'm so excited.
ドキドキ
Play with your feet.
足あそんで
It's really fun.
めっちゃ楽しい
terrible.
やばい
It's already the best.
もう最高じゃん
Super harem.
超ハーレム
Let's get married, three of us.
3人で結婚しよう
fun.
楽しい
amazing.
すごい
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Very standing.
超立ってる
I feel like I'm doing something wrong.
悪いことしてる気分
Yes, that's right.
ええそう
He's greedy.
欲しがりさんだ
I'm a greedy person.
欲しがりさんなの
Mr. Covetous.
欲しがりさん
Just looking at it like that.
そんな見てるだけ
Let's decide.
判断しようかな
I'm watching.
見てる
I'm observing.
観察してる
観 察 して る
being observed.
観察されてる
Man car hits.
マンカー当たる
Feels good.
気持ちいい
one
一
Together?
緒 に?
together.
一緒に
difficult.
難しい
Kintama or something?
キンタマとか?
Shall I go down?
私は下に下がりましょうか
amazing.
すごい
Sister, will you make this baby?
お姉さんこの子作る?
I'll take turns.
交代します
I made eye contact with the embarrassed older sister.
恥ずかしいお姉さんと目が合う
Let's take a look at this.
ちょっと見ちゃうなこれ
cute.
かわいい
Erotic.
エロい
Very
めっちゃ
I feel like saying it.
言 えたくなってきちゃった
Can you say it?
言えるの?
Which way?
どっちに?
Since there are two of us, I can tell them both.
2人いるんだから2人に言えちゃうよ
Do you play rock, paper, scissors?
じゃんけんする?
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
First.
先
Either is fine.
どっちでもいいよ
I can't choose, so I play rock, paper, scissors.
選べないからじゃんけんして
retirement.
退職
I won.
勝 った
Who wins?
勝ったほうがどっち?
yes.
はい
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
After and ahead.
後と先
I want to see your sister first.
先にお姉さんの見たいね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
That's a lie, right?
嘘でしょ
Is that possible?
その展開ありなの
Because.
だって
Okay.
オッケー
Are you feeling good?
気上いいですか?
Sister.
お姉さん
Are there two people watching from below?
下から2人に見られてるのかな?
Is it new?
新しいかな?
Still a mess.
まだめちゃめちゃ
It's in.
入ってる
Look carefully.
よーく見て
Get on top?
上に乗る?
Which one is better?
どれがいい?
Leave it to me.
任せる
What should I do?
どうしたらいい?
Do you have this?
これがある?
Which way?
どっちに?
like.
好き
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look.
見て
I'll come in.
入るよ
Excuse me.
失礼します
amazing.
すごい
There's a lot in it.
すごい入ってる
amazing.
すごい
Super erotic.
超エロい
It's slimy.
ヌルヌルしてる
It's my kind, right?
自分の種類でしょ
No.
違うよ
Is it your sister's type?
お姉さんの種類か
No.
違うよ
It's hot.
熱いね
熱いです
I don't understand from the two of you.
2人から分かんない
Please let me in, sister.
入れてもらお姉さん
Leave it to me.
任せて
Don't sleep on my waist.
腰に寝ないでね
difficult?
難しい?
difficult.
難しい
Do you like bags?
バック好き?
I like it.
好きです
Beautiful back.
背中綺麗
Beautiful eyes.
目が綺麗
amazing.
すごい
There's a lot in it.
すごい入ってる
amazing.
すごい
My butt is plump.
お尻がぷよぷよしてる
Will you back me too?
私もバックしてくれるの?
Do you know?
知って?
i don't know.
知らない
Put it in.
入れて
Try putting it in.
入れてみて
Here.
ここに
Just touch me.
ちょっと触って
Taste it.
味わってみて
Would you like to try this?
これ入れてみる?
Put this in.
これ入れて
He said it was smart.
それスマタって言ってた
Try it.
やってみて
Rub it.
こすって
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's true.
当たる
So I touched the older sister's breasts from behind.
それでお姉さんの後ろからおっぱい触って
I'm sweating.
汗かいてる
I'll lick your sweat.
汗を舐めてあげる
It looks like he's spitting out his dick.
おチンチン吐いてるみたいだね
That's naughty.
エッチだね
This makes me tickle.
ムズムズしちゃうこれ
Can I come in?
入 れてもいい?
Put it in.
入れて
amazing.
すごい
Is it in?
入ってる?
There's a lot in it.
すごい入ってる
I want to see you vomit from your ass.
お尻から吐いてるところ見たいな
You can take it out once.
抜いてもいいよ一回
behind.
後ろ
Oh no.
やば
Erotic.
エロい
amazing.
すごい
Look at the front.
前の目になってみて
Look, it's completely visible.
ほ ら、丸見え
Erotic.
エロい
That's amazing.
すごいよ
If you're coming from that direction, would you mind if I happened to touch it?
そっちからくるとですと、たまたま触ってもらっていい?
Because it's both.
両方ですから
A luxurious person.
贅沢な人
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
You can't see it completely right now.
丸見えないもんね今ね
I can't move.
動けないね
I can't move
動けなくなっちゃう
Yo.
よ
Super beautiful butt.
超 お尻きれい
Should I try putting clothes on the back?
後ろ服入れてみる?
Sister.
お姉様
Oh, me?
あ、私?
Is it my turn this time?
今度は私のターンなの?
Before I knew it, I was being called big sister.
いつの間にかお姉様って呼ばれてる
That's right.
そうだよね
I'll call you a big sister here.
ここでお姉様ってやる
Your sister is here, right?
ここでお姉様でしょ?
difficult.
難しい
Enter it from here.
こっちから入れるの
difficult.
難しい
Oh no.
やば
Feels good.
気持ちいい
This butt is so erotic.
このお尻エロいよね
I feel like doing something like this.
なんかこうやってしたくなっちゃう
You can wear it.
着けていいよ
It's getting wetter and wetter.
どんどんどんどん濡れてくるね
Because I hear erotic sounds from behind.
後ろからエロい音が聞こえるから
It's difficult though.
難しいんだけど
hello.
もしもし
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Did you take a look from below?
下から覗いてみた?
happy.
うれしい
Is it pretty and fun?
ときれい楽しい?
fun.
楽しい
So beautiful.
すごいきれい
Take it out again and go home.
もう一回出して帰って
It was out, but it's still amazing.
出てたけどさ、なんかまだすごいよ
I have to go back to my sister.
お姉様に戻らないといけない
Because I'm jealous.
嫉妬するから
I'm waiting.
待ってる
It feels so good that it's going to get bigger soon.
気持ちいいからすぐ大きくなっちゃうよ
It's gotten bigger.
大きくなっちゃった
It's gotten bigger, hasn't it?
大きくなっちゃったよね
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってる
Will it come out?
出るかな?
Sister, would you like to go?
お姉さん行ってみる?
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
That's enough.
もういいです
difficult?
難しい?
difficult.
難しい
amazing.
すごい
You were ready.
準備万端だったね
There are a lot of them.
いっぱい出てる
It's fun girls.
女の子楽しいですね
fun.
楽 しい
fine?
元気?
I'm fine.
元気です
How are you here?
ここ元気?
Please take care of yourself over there.
あそこ元気にしてください
It moved a lot.
いっぱい動いたもんね
I moved a lot and put it out.
いっぱい動いて出しちゃったし
I like it here.
私、ここが好きなんだよ
where?
どこ?
Is that so?
そうなの?
This is what I like about men.
男の人のここが好きなの
I'm glad I fell off and stopped.
よかったから落ちてやすめて
Okay, here it is.
いいよね、ここね
Here.
ここの
Yes, it's a line.
そう、ラインね
I understand.
わかる
Chinchin, good evening.
ち んちん、こんばんは
Good evening, Dondon.
こんばんは、どんどん
how are you?
元気ですか?
Sorry, I'm an idiot.
ごめんね、アホで
I'm fine.
元気です
If you had a mouth, you'd say you'd like to talk.
お口があったら喋りたいって言ったらね、
I'm sure.
きっとね
I hope you're fine.
元気ですよってね
Do you like to shave?
ヘラするの好き?
It's kind of cute how you do it.
なんか、いまいちやり方が、 かわいい
Aren't you the one who was indoctrinated?
教え込まれた人じゃない?
Looks like I understand.
分かったみたいな
I don't know how to do it properly.
うまいやり方が、分かんなくて
cute.
かわいい
Are you going to tell me?
教えてあげるの?
let's.
しよう
What?
え、なに?
Give me a little lick a lot.
ちょっといっぱいペロペロしてあげて
I'll be waiting, dick.
待ってます、おちんちん
Where do you start?
どこから、どこからしますか?
What, are you going this way?
え、こっちに行くの?
I would like a gold ball flower please.
金玉玉花お願いします
Maybe here, here?
ここかな、ここ?
Yeah, good at it.
うん、上手
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですね
I started talking.
話し入れちゃった
good?
上手?
He's my senior.
先輩だ
Wait, I'm being watched a lot.
待って、めっちゃ見られてる
Lick?
なめる?
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
Isn't your mouth small?
お口ちっちゃくない?
cute.
かわいい
You did a good job.
上手にできましたね
No, you're good at it.
いや、上手だよ
It's erotic to watch.
見ててエロってなる
Well then, I'll be in charge of the bottom.
じゃあ、私は下を担当します
Were you in charge?
担当性があったの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's super luxurious.
超贅沢だよ
thank you.
ありがたい
You'll be in charge.
下担当になるじゃん
I'm feeling really energetic.
めっちゃ元気になってる
When I did it earlier.
さっきもしたときに
If it's gotten to this point, I'll have to ask someone to take care of it over the phone.
ここまでだったら電話で面倒見てもらわないと
What do you like?
何が好きなの?
What do you like after all?
結局何が好きなの?
Seiran and Teko.
セイランとテコね
I like Ossex.
オセックスが好きです
You know that.
それは知ってるよね
Everyone knows that.
それは誰もが知ってるよね
Super hard.
超固い
Is it okay if I take this out?
これ出したってもいいの?
Okay.
いいよ
Shall we do it together?
一緒にする?
big.
大きい
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってる
Looks like it's about to come out.
出ちゃいそうだよ
Okay.
いいよ
amazing.
すごい
It's out.
出たー
amazing.
すごい
It's really flying.
めっちゃ飛んでる
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It was terrible.
やばかった
I haven't touched it yet.
まだ触らないから
I think I can do it again.
もう 一回できそう
Super energetic.
超元気
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
me too.
私も